Good morning and good afternoon, and welcome to everyone to our Q1 2026 conference call.
The information presented today contains forward-looking statements that involve known
and unknown risks, uncertainties, and other factors. These may cause actual results to be
materially different from any future results, performance, or achievements expressed or
implied by such statements. For a description of some of these factors, please refer to the
company's Form 20F and its most recent quarterly results on Form 6K that respectively were filed
with and furnished to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission. Before we get started,
I also want to echo Sharon. Please limit yourselves to one question at a time,
and we will cycle through the queue as needed. And with that, I will hand across to Vas.
Thank you, Sloan, and thanks, everyone, for joining today's call. So if we go to slide four,
as you saw this morning, we delivered a strong start to the year.
Across our priority brands and launches, which is really where our focus is at the moment,
these brands and launches are what's going to drive our mid- to long-term growth,
and where we believe now we have demonstrated that there's strong momentum behind these medicines.
The details for the quarter, you saw that those growth drivers were up 34%
in constant currency. Our base business was largely stable, but we did see significant
GX erosions, as we've guided to. And Mukul will go through some of the dynamics,
and we'll cover that over the course of the rest of the year. On core op-inc, we were down 14%,
driven by the sales decline, as well as the increased investments in R&D, which we also
guided to. When you look at some of the pipeline highlights, a number of important highlights,
including the continued progress for Rapsido across the number of indications,
Unalamab received a breakthrough therapy designation and priority review in Sjogren's
disease, as well as a few other important milestones, which we'll go over over the course of the call.
Importantly, we're maintaining our full-year sales and core operating guidance for the year.
Now, moving to the next slide, when you look at those growth drivers in a little bit more detail,
that 34% was driven in particular by very strong performance we saw in Cascali,
Fluvicto, Casimta, Lecvio, driven by our strong launch overseas, particularly in China,
and the continued performance of Semblok. So I'll look forward to going through now some of
the dynamics for each of our key brands over the course of the year.
Now, moving to slide six, in quarter one, Cascali grew 55%. And as you know, Cascali now